from light into being
turret deployed turret online
aligning defense system defenses in
place
turret in place sentry deployed
sentry turret placed sentry online
[Music]
prakash sejivani
my teleporter is online
my turret was destroyed my defenses are
weakened
intruder detected my sentry was
destroyed
reality bends to my will
oh
hmm
the true enemy of humanity is disorder
if everyone performs their function
victory is assured
do not deviate from the plan and victory
will be ours
i will shape order from chaos
order will be restored
a momentary lapse death
is an illusion my work is not complete
i will correct my mistakes
i will follow my path
there is still much to be done
much better i am restored
i am on fire
an exceptional performance
i have reached peak performance levels
my full potential is unlocked
my power grows
system optimized our fates are entwined
perfect alignment
i am unstoppable
there is nothing that will stand in my
way
damn a performance worthy of repetition
ah that is the way
as it should be i will show you the path
they have revived they have returned to
the fight
a second chance symmetra reporting
sniper i have located the enemy
enemy turret ahead
the enemy possesses a teleporter we must
locate it
we must locate the teleporter
enemy teleporter located we must destroy
it
behind you do not let up
victory will soon be ours
if we work in unison our defense will be
impenetrable
defend together it will not be long now
attack now or we are defeated
secure the objective time grows
short but we will fight to the end
time is running out we must not fail
align our attack move the payload
i am at the objective we must take it
quickly
i am claiming the objective support me
i am taking the objective all is going
according to plan
we must hold the point against that
attack
reinforce our defenses we must turn them
back
consolidate our defenses on the point
the payload moves as must we
the payload moves to its destination all
according to plan
the payload is moving converge upon it
the payload is moving we must pull
together
together we must stop the payload this
is the way it must be
we must stop the payload the payload has
stopped
we must get it moving the payload has
we must get our plan back on track
just as expected order is restored
the balance shifts in my favor
hmm perception is your weakness
why do you struggle against your fate
you are unworthy of the true reality
know your place perfection
you are trapped in your own mind
this is the order of things
that was for your own good you lack
imagination
ah you were not meant for greatness
all according to plan
a punishment for your crimes
order overcomes chaos
everything in its place a pattern
develops
this is the shape of things to come
enemy turret destroyed an inferior
design
enemy turret destroyed
enemy teleporter destroyed
get back know your place
shameful you perform your function
admirably well executed
i had not forgotten you
the enemy team has been eliminated
all enemies eliminated
hello hello
[Music]
greetings namaste
thank you you have my thanks
understood i understand
acknowledged i need healing
i require healing form up
group up group up with me
group up here my ultimate is charging
my teleporter is almost ready to deploy
my ultimate is almost ready
my ultimate ability is ready teleporter
ready for deployment
my teleporter is ready to deploy
such a lack of imagination
am i supposed to be impressed
everything by design
exquisite how unsightly
i don't think so
impressive perfect
harmony precisely
i will put you in your place
welcome to my reality
why do you struggle
hard work and dedication pays off
victory is everything what a frightening
thought
the treat is a lie
do not believe everything you see
i made you something were you expecting
a miracle
beauty can be found where everything is
in harmony
good fortune
cause for celebration
if i can think it i can create it
kindly adjust i've taken your opinion on
the advisement
ah time pass
who knows what the future holds
setting up the car wash
what interesting ways your mind works
let us discuss your failures
huh so dramatic
to think i should have to work with a
straight ruffian
what you call freedom is an illusion
that causes more harm than good
what do you call freedom i call anarchy
vishkar is building a better future for
humanity
you should return what you stole from
vishkar
of course science obeys the laws of
nature
it is only to be expected
armor how positively medieval
no there isn't
this would be a perfect location for a
vishkar development
from here it all looks to be so orderly
and peaceful
teleportation portal opened we move
swiftly
teleportation portal opened
shield well summoned you are protected
creating a barrier projecting a barrier
projecting barrier i will
shield you i will shield us
this will protect you this will protect
us
barrier is on its way photon barrier
deployed
instancing photon barrier
shield engaged i will shield you
be shielded you are shielded
shield matrix established
everyone is protected
turret available for deployment
defensive matrix established
there is a gap in my defense matrix
teleporter online i have opened the path
teleporter online we move swiftly
shield generator online you are
protected
shield generator online defense matrix
established
shield matrix established protect the
teleporter
my teleporter is under attack
my shield generator is under attack
teleporter destroyed my teleporter has
been destroyed
my teleporter has been destroyed the
path is closed
my teleporter has been destroyed the way
is closed
teleporter offline my teleporter is
offline
teleporter offline the path is closed
my teleporter is offline the path is
closed
my teleporter is offline the way is
my shield generator has been destroyed
my shield generator is offline
you